- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
kids: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
孩子们：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
All:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
♪ ♪
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[relaxing beachy music]
[轻松的海滩音乐]
♪ ♪
[upbeat jazz music]
[欢快的爵士乐]
- And now back
to "The Kelpbed Kids."
- 现在回来了
到“海带孩子”。
- "The Kelpbed Kids"
are hilarious.
- “海带孩子”
很搞笑。
High four!
高四！
[both laugh]
[两人都笑了]
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
- Wonder why
it's in black and white.
- 想知道为什么
它是黑白的。
- It's a "artistical" choice.
- 这是一个“艺术”的选择。
- All right, Kelpbed Kids.
- 好吧，海带孩子们。
Youse gonna spill the beans
你会泄露秘密
about where you hide
all your candy
关于你藏身的地方
你所有的糖果
in this here clubhouse or else!
在这个俱乐部会所或者其他地方！
- Not to you, Ajax.
- 不是对你来说，阿贾克斯。
- We'll never tell you
that it's in the cabinet.
- 我们永远不会告诉你
它在内阁里。
[Kelpbed Kids groan]
[海带孩子们呻吟]
Oh. Sorry, gang.
哦。对不起，帮派。
[all grumble]
[大家抱怨]
- Hey, Patrick,
don't the Kelpbed Kids
- 嘿，帕特里克，
海带孩子们不是吗
kinda look like people we know?
看起来有点像我们认识的人？
[glass shatters]
[玻璃碎裂]
- I don't know
any people we know.
- 我不知道
我们认识的任何人。
[gargles, spits]
[漱口、吐口水]
Hmm. Eee!
唔。哎呀！
- Oh-ho-ho-ho.
The cabinet, you say.
- 哦，嗬，嗬，嗬。
你说的是内阁。
Aha!
啊哈！
All: Hoops?
- [belches]
全体：篮球？
- [打嗝]
Hi, Ajax.
嗨，阿贾克斯。
- It's empty.
- 空了。
I'm gonna give everyone here
我要给这里的每个人
and their old man
a knuckle sandwich.
和他们的老人
指关节三明治
- Oh boy! With cheese?
- 天啊！加奶酪？
- With cheese.
- 配奶酪。
- Oh, no you don't,
you dizzy ding dong.
- 哦，不，你不，
你头晕叮咚。
Hwah!
哇！
- Huh?
- 啊？
[lively jazz music]
[活泼的爵士乐]
Whuh?
呃？
[laughs]
[笑]
- Hey, what gives? Let me go.
- 嘿，什么给了？让我走吧。
- You just got hooped.
- 你刚刚被套住了。
All: Hoops, Hoops,
Hoops, Hoops!
所有： 篮圈，篮圈，
篮球，篮球！
Both: Hoops, Hoops,
Hoops, Hoops!
两者：圈圈，圈圈，
篮球，篮球！
- That settles it.
=> - 这就解决了。
Hoops is
our favorite Kelpbed Kid.
篮球是
我们最喜欢的海藻小子。
Let's get out
our official Hoops hoops
我们出去吧
我们的官方篮球圈
that I bought on SeaBay.
我在SeaBay上买的。
- Way ahead of ya, pally.
- 遥遥领先于你，伙计。
- Gah!
- Hey, mine shrunk.
- 啊！
- 嘿，我的缩小了。
- Oh, no, Patrick.
It's adjustable.
- 哦，不，帕特里克。
它是可调节的。
Who says a hoop has to be round?
谁说箍一定是圆的？
- Oh, yeah.
There's a relaxed-fit button.
- 哦，是的。
有一个宽松纽扣。
Ah.
啊。
- Someone wrote
all over my hula hoop.
- 有人写道
遍布我的呼啦圈。
- Hey, there's an address
printed on here.
- 嘿，有一个地址
印在这里。
And it's in Bikini Bottom.
它位于比基尼泳裤中。
Do you think
it's where Hoops lives?
你认为
这是Hoops住的地方吗？
Could we? Should we?
我们可以吗？我们应该吗？
- Ring his doorbell
and run away?
- 按他的门铃
然后逃跑？
- No.
- Toilet-paper his house?
- 不。
- 他家有卫生纸吗？
- No.
- Switch out
- 不。
- 关掉
his regular for decaf?
他常喝脱咖啡因咖啡？
- No. We can meet him.
- 不，我们可以见到他。
- Gotcha.
- 明白了。
We can meet him,
then toilet-paper his house.
我们可以见到他，
然后用卫生纸给他的房子。
He's gonna need it
after the coffee.
他会需要它
喝完咖啡后。
[toilet flushing]
[冲厕所]
- This is it...
where Hoops lives.
- 就是这个...
霍普斯住的地方。
- It's a palace.
- 这是一座宫殿。
[tense music]
[紧张的音乐]
♪ ♪
- I'm too nervous to knock.
We don't really know him.
- 我太紧张了，不敢敲门。
我们并不真正了解他。
What if he's one of
those suffering artist types
如果他是其中之一怎么办
那些受苦受难的艺术家类型
who are into witchcraft?
谁沉迷于巫术？
- Or what if he's a cannibal
and wants to eat us?
- 或者如果他是一个食人者怎么办
还想吃我们？
- What if he's a cannibal
and doesn't want to eat us?
- 如果他是一个食人者怎么办
并不想吃掉我们？
- We couldn't live
with the shame.
- 我们无法生活
带着羞耻。
[doorknob clicking]
[门把手咔哒声]
Oh, shh!
哦，嘘！
Both: Run!
两人：跑！
- [humming happily]
- [高兴地哼哼]
- Old Man Walker?
- 老沃克？
What's he doing in Hoops' house?
他在霍普斯家里做什么？
Maybe we got the wrong house.
也许我们找错了房子。
- Oh.
- 哦。
He's sad that he got no mail.
- [chomps]
他很遗憾没有收到邮件。
- [咀嚼]
That's 'cause I got it.
那是因为我明白了。
- It's addressed to Hoops.
This is the right place.
- 是写给 Hoops 的。
这是正确的地方。
- Whoa.
- 哇哦。
The whole house is filled
with "Kelpbed Kid" stuff.
整个房子都被占满了
和“Kelpbed Kid”的东西。
- It's just like being
in the show.
- 就像是
在节目中。
Come on in.
- Don't mind if I do.
进来吧。
- 如果我这样做的话，请不要介意。
- [grunts] What's happening?
- [咕哝]发生什么事了？
[thunderous footsteps]
[雷鸣般的脚步声]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
♪ ♪
- [snarls]
- [咆哮]
- [gasps] Is that Hoops?
- [喘气] 那是篮球吗？
- Uh, no.
It's Old Man Walker again.
- 呃，不。
又是老沃克。
Remember? From the mailbox?
记住？从邮箱里发来的？
- [retches] Oh, yeah.
- [干呕]哦，是的。
- Hooligans! Swindlers!
Letter looters!
- 流氓！骗子！
信掠夺者！
- Oh, we didn't mean any harm!
- 哦，我们没有任何恶意！
We just wanted to meet Hoops.
我们只是想见见霍普斯。
We're fans.
- We love Hoops!
我们是粉丝。
- 我们喜欢篮球！
- Huh? Hoops?
- 啊？篮球？
Why didn't you say so?
你为什么不这么说？
[beeping]
[嘟嘟声]
I'm Hoops!
我是霍普斯！
[both laugh]
[两人都笑了]
- Okay, old man.
- 好吧，老伙计。
- Uh, I hate to break it to you,
- 呃，我不想打扰你，
but Hoops is a little kid.
但霍普斯还是个小孩子。
- Yup, I was Hoops
when I was a little kid,
- 是的，我是篮球
当我还是个小孩子的时候
many years ago.
许多年前。
- You're telling me
there have been many years?
- 你在告诉我
已经有很多年了？
I don't believe it.
我不相信。
- Yes, it was in the past.
- 是的，那是过去的事了。
- I think you're trying
to "past" one over on us.
- 我想你正在努力
向我们“过去”一件事。
- "Past" one over.
——《往事》一过。
[laughing]
[笑]
I don't get it.
我不明白。
- Huh? What are you, a couple
of dizzy ding dongs?
- 啊？你们是什么啊，情侣
头晕的叮咚声？
- Hey, he said
Hoops' catchphrase.
- 嘿，他说
霍普斯的口头禅。
"Ya dizzy ding dongs."
“呀，头晕叮咚。”
- Ya dizzy ding dongs.
- 呀，头晕叮咚。
[both gasp]
[两人都喘气]
- Patrick,
"Old Man" Walker is Hoops!
- 帕特里克，
“老头子”沃克是篮球人！
He just kinda, sorta, decayed.
他只是有点，有点，腐烂了。
- [gasps] Hoops!
- [喘气] 篮球！
We love you!
- Oh!
我们爱你！
- 哦！
You're breaking my bones.
你正在打断我的骨头。
- Hey, he's got
a new catchphrase.
- 嘿，他有
一个新的流行语。
[metallic clank]
[金属叮当声]
- What was that?
- Was that my heart?
- 那是什么？
- 那是我的心吗？
- Uh, no, it was outside.
- 呃，不，是在外面。
- Huh? My heart's outside?
- 啊？我的心在外面吗？
Oh, not again.
哦，不会了。
- [cackles]
- [咯咯笑]
- Aah!
- 啊啊！
- Ow!
- Yum.
- 噢！
- 嗯。
- Dagnabbit, it's that ruffian,
Ajax McGee.
- Dagnabbit，就是那个恶棍，
阿贾克斯·麦基.
- Ajax? Isn't he the mean kid
in "The Kelpbed Kids" show?
- 阿贾克斯？他不是那个卑鄙的孩子吗
- He was.
- 他是。
Now he's the mean adult
现在他是个卑鄙的成年人了
at Shady Shoals Retirement Home.
在谢迪肖尔斯退休之家。
Oh!
哦！
- That's what you get
for being a Kelpbed Kid,
- 这就是你得到的
作为一个海带孩子，
Hoops the Poops.
圈住便便。
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
- [gulps, laughs]
Hoops the Poops.
- [吞咽，大笑]
圈住便便。
Classic.
经典的。
Hey, I just had an idea.
Revenge.
嘿，我只是有一个主意。
复仇。
Let's get back at Ajax,
like in one of your episodes.
就像你的其中一集一样。
- Huh, episodes?
- 呃，剧集？
Yeah, at my age,
I have a lot of episodes.
是的，在我这个年纪，
Who wants pudding?
- I do!
谁想要布丁？
- 我愿意！
- Hold that pudding.
- 拿着那个布丁。
We can build our own tank,
我们可以建造自己的坦克，
and we'll gather material
"The Kelpbed Kids" way.
“海带孩子”方式。
- Eh, the what bed
who... wait, what?
- 呃，什么床
谁……等等，什么？
[both laughing]
[两人都笑了]
both: Classic Hoops.
两者：经典篮球。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [moaning]
- [呻吟]
- [humming] Huh?
- [哼哼] 嗯？
[both laugh]
[两人都笑了]
both: Ah!
两人：啊！
[both groan]
[两人都呻吟]
- Hmm?
- 唔？
♪ ♪
[laughter]
[笑声]
[bikers scream]
[骑自行车的人尖叫]
[clicking, whirring]
[咔哒声，呼呼声]
- We're coming for you,
Ajax McGee!
- 我们来找你了
阿贾克斯·麦基！
- Say hello
to my Meanie Mangler!
- 打个招呼
致我的米妮·曼格勒！
[triumphant music]
[胜利的音乐]
♪ ♪
- Here we are, Hoops.
Shady Shoals.
- 我们到了，霍普斯。
阴暗浅滩。
Now call out for Ajax.
现在呼叫阿贾克斯。
- Eh? Huh? Who am I calling?
- 呃？啊？ Who am I calling?
- Talk into this.
- Hello, operator?
- 谈谈这个。
- 你好，接线员？
This is Barracuda 4117.
这是梭子鱼 4117。
Is my prescription ready yet?
我的处方准备好了吗？
- 23 Skiddoo.
- 23 斯基杜。
Hey, where did you get
that pile of junk?
嘿，你从哪里得到的
那堆垃圾？
Never mind, I don't care.
Have some eggs!
没关系，我不在乎。
吃点鸡蛋吧！
- Whoa! Prepare cannon.
- 哇！准备大炮。
Fire!
火！
- Huh?
- 啊？
- Uh, you loaded the cannon
with toast?
- 呃，你装上了大炮
配吐司？
- I always have toast with eggs.
- 我总是吃鸡蛋吐司。
- Deploying salt lick.
- 部署舔盐。
♪ ♪
Engaging sea cow.
参与海牛。
- [moos]
- [哞哞]
- Eugh. Ooh. Ew. Ugh.
- 呃。哦。呃。啊。
Your tongue is so rough!
你的舌头太粗糙了！
- Huh?
- Hmm? [screams]
- 啊？
- 唔？ [尖叫声]
- [snickers]
- [窃笑]
[Klaxon blares]
- [yowls]
[喇叭声]
- [嚎叫]
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- Whoa!
- 哇！
Whoa, whoa! Aah!
Everything smells like toast!
哇哦！啊啊！
一切都闻起来像吐司！
[all wailing]
[全体哀嚎]
- Aah!
- 啊啊！
[grunts]
- [groans]
[咕哝]
- [呻吟]
[pinball sounds chiming]
[弹球声响起]
[all grunting and screaming]
[所有的咕哝声和尖叫声]
[laughter]
[笑声]
[all groaning weakly]
[所有人都微弱地呻吟]
[bright music]
[明亮的音乐]
- Look, there goes Ajax.
- 看，阿贾克斯来了。
- I'll get youse next time!
- 下次我给你买！
- Say my name.
I'm Hoops the Poops.
- 说出我的名字。
我是胡普斯。
- Classic.
- 经典的。
Both: Best "Kelpbed Kids"
adventure ever!
两者：最佳“海带孩子”
永远的冒险！
High four!
高四！
[both laugh]
[两人都笑了]
- Oops. Uh...
- Aah!
- 哎呀。呃...
- 啊啊！
- Just call me Hoops the Oops.
- 就叫我“Hoops the Oops”吧。
[laughs]
[笑]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[all meeping insistently]
[所有人都坚持不懈地嘀咕着]
- Okay, okay, one at a time.
- 好吧，好吧，一次一个。
Krabby Patty!
- Krabby Patty!
蟹蟹帕蒂！
- 螃蟹帕蒂！
- Krabby Patty, up!
- 克拉比帕蒂，起来！
- Krabby Patty!
- 螃蟹帕蒂！
- Krabby Patty, up!
- 克拉比帕蒂，起来！
- Meep, meep.
- 米普，米普。
- Oh, all this meeping is gonna
drive me cuckoo, Mr. Krabs.
- 哦，所有这些meeping都会
蟹老板，给我带来杜鹃鸟。
- All these meeps
are paying your salary.
- 所有这些meeps
正在支付你的工资。
Meeps are money.
- Krabby Patty!
米普就是钱。
- 螃蟹帕蒂！
- Krabby Patty!
- Krabby Patty, up!
- 克拉比帕蒂，起来！
[munching]
[咀嚼]
[loud gulping, belching]
[大声吞咽，打嗝]
[meeping]
[嘀咕]
- Wait, someone ordered
a Krabby Patty to-go.
- 等等，有人下令了
蟹肉饼外卖。
Who ordered
a Krabby Patty to-go?
谁订购的
蟹黄饼外卖？
Whoa!
哇！
Wait, whose order is this?
等等，这是谁的命令？
Whoa. Okay.
哇哦。好的。
[meeping]
[嘀咕]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
Pardon me, did someone order
a Krabby...
抱歉，有人下单吗
一个蟹蟹...
[sighs oddly]
[奇怪地叹气]
Oh, um, my bad.
I meant meep, meep.
哦，嗯，​​我的错。
我的意思是米普，米普。
- Oh, meep.
- 哦，米普。
Meep, meep.
[cash register dings]
米普，米普。
[收银机叮叮声]
- Meep.
- 米普。
[laughs]
[笑]
[meeping]
[嘀咕]
Oh boy, ice meep.
哦，孩子，冰米普。
♪ ♪
[tires screeching]
[轮胎的尖叫声]
[rhythmic meeping]
Yeah.
[有节奏的喵喵声]
是的。
Real meep, daddy-o.
真是的，爸爸。
[meeping excitedly]
[兴奋地嘀咕]
Bouncy, bouncy!
Bouncy, bouncy, bouncy!
弹跳，弹跳！
弹跳，弹跳，弹跳！
I love to meep.
[laughs]
我喜欢meep。
[笑]
- Meep, meep!
- 米普，米普！
- Meep!
- 米普！
Meep, meep, meep.
米普，米普，米普。
[doorbell chimes]
Meep?
[门铃响]
米普？
Meep, meep, meep.
米普，米普，米普。
- Hey, SpongeBob.
- 嘿，海绵宝宝。
These palms are ready to play
some serious patty-cake.
这些手掌已准备好玩耍
一些正宗的馅饼。
- Meep.
- 米普。
- And you can't play patty-cake
- 而且你不能玩小馅饼
without cake.
- Meep!
没有蛋糕。
- 米普！
- Patty-cake, patty-cake.
- Meep-meep-meep, meep-meep...
- 馅饼，馅饼。
- 喵喵喵，喵喵喵……
- Baker's man, I'll eat
the cake as fast as I can.
- 面包师的人，我来吃
尽可能快地做蛋糕。
Mama called the doctor,
and the doctor said,
妈妈打电话给医生，
医生说，
"No more patty-cakes jumping
on the bed."
“不再有馅饼跳跃
在床上。”
Meep, meep, meep.
米普，米普，米普。
- Meep, meep mah-meep,
meep, meep, meep, meep, meep.
- 米普，米普，玛米普，
米普，米普，米普，米普，米普。
- Meep, meep, meep.
- Mailman!
- 米普，米普，米普。
- 邮递员！
- Meep.
[both meeping]
- 米普。
[两人都嘀咕着]
- Morning, SpongeBob.
Morning, Patrick.
- 早上好，海绵宝宝。
早上好，帕特里克。
[Klaxon blares]
[喇叭声]
[both meeping]
[两人都嘀咕着]
No!
不！
[all meeping]
[大家都在嘀咕]
- It's about time, SpongeBob.
- 是时候了，海绵宝宝。
LateBob is more like it.
LateBob 更喜欢它。
Ha, LateBob.
[laughs, snorts]
哈，迟到的鲍勃。
[大笑，哼哼]
- When you're done snorting,
- 当你吸完鼻涕后
I'd like to order
a Krabby Patty.
我想订购
蟹肉饼。
- Okay, hold on. [laughs]
- [growls]
- 好吧，等一下。 [笑]
- [咆哮]
- One Krabby Patty, SpongeBob.
- 一只蟹蟹饼、海绵宝宝。
- Meep, meep.
- 米普，米普。
Meep, meep, meep. Meep.
米普，米普，米普。米普。
Meep, meep, meep, meep,
meep, meep, meep, meep.
米普，米普，米普，米普，
米普，米普，米普，米普。
Meep.
- [gulping] Meep.
米普。
- [吞咽]米普。
- SpongeBob, stop that meeping.
- 海绵宝宝，别再发出喵喵声了。
What do you think you are?
An anchovy?
你以为你是什么？
凤尾鱼？
- Oof!
- I hear money meeps.
- 噢！
- 我听到钱的声音。
Are the anchovies back?
凤尾鱼回来了吗？
- It's SpongeBob.
- [meeping]
- 这是海绵宝宝。
- [嘀咕]
- SpongeBob!
- 海绵宝宝！
What in the barnacles
is going on here?
藤壶里有什么
这是怎么回事？
- [squeals] [all meeping]
- [尖叫声] [全部发出喵喵声]
- Oh, di-doo. Oh.
- 哦，迪杜。哦。
[all meeping]
Huh?
[大家都在嘀咕]
啊？
- [growls, barks]
- [咆哮，吠叫]
- Step aside and let
my precious Fifi pass,
- 靠边让
我珍贵的菲菲通行证，
or I will be offended.
否则我会被冒犯。
Oh!
哦！
Meep?
Both: Meep!
米普？
两人：喵！
[both laughing]
[两人都笑了]
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
- Huh?
- 啊？
It's a stamp-meep!
这是一张邮票！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Phew.
[gasps]
唷。
[喘气]
Meep. Meep, meep, meep.
米普。米普，米普，米普。
- Bob Gale Doppler,
with the big weather.
- 鲍勃·盖尔·多普勒，
随着大天气。
And I'd like to report it's
sunny skies for Bikini Bottom.
我想报告的是
比基尼泳裤的天空晴朗。
But not today, cause there's
a storm warning coming at ya.
但今天不行，因为有
风暴警告即将向您发出。
We got a gust of faux-chovies
coming in from the southwest.
我们尝到了一股人造chovies的味道
从西南方向进来。
Now with a closer look,
here's our man on the street,
现在仔细一看，
这是我们在街上的那个人，
Rube Goldfish.
鲁布金鱼。
- Thanks, Gale.
- 谢谢，盖尔。
I'm here with the faux-chovies
我带着假chovies来了
that are causing all
this meep-abaloo.
导致所有
这个meep-abaloo。
Now I just have
to ask the question
现在我只有
提出问题
everyone wants to know.
每个人都想知道。
What in the world
does "meep" mean?
世界上有什么
"meep" 是什么意思？
[all chanting meeps]
[所有人都在喊口号]
Ameeping.
阿米普。
- Haha, thanks Rube.
- 哈哈，谢谢鲁布。
So if you don't wanna turn
into an anchovy today,
所以如果你不想转身
今天变成凤尾鱼，
you're advised to stay indoors
建议您呆在室内
until that faux-chovy
pressure system moves away.
直到那个假chovy
压力系统移开。
Ha ha.
[all meeping]
哈哈。
[大家都在嘀咕]
Huh? Whoa!
啊？哇！
[struggling]
[挣扎]
Ha ha, meep.
哈哈，米普。
- Ah.
And now it's Squiddy time.
- 啊。
现在是鱿鱼时间。
Hoo! Ha ha, mm.
呼！哈哈，嗯。
[scatting]
[分散]
When the customers fizzle,
当顾客不欢而散时，
the octopus will sizzle.
章鱼会发出嘶嘶声。
Ha, yeah.
哈，是的。
[feet pattering]
[脚打颤]
[faint meeping]
[微弱的喵喵声]
[together] Meep, meep!
Dinner, dinner.
[合] 喵喵！
晚餐，晚餐。
Meep, meep. Dinner, dinner.
- Whoa!
米普，米普。晚餐，晚餐。
- 哇！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
SpongeBob and Mr. Krabs
are faux-chovies?
海绵宝宝和蟹老板
是假chovies吗？
- Meep, meep.
- 米普，米普。
- Okay, okay. Slow down.
- 好吧，好吧。减速。
One Krabby Patty,
one Krabby Patty,
一份蟹肉饼，
one Krabby Patty.
一份蟹肉饼。
- Meep.
[all meeping]
- 米普。
[大家都在嘀咕]
- Whoever wants a Krabby Patty,
raise your hand.
- 谁想要蟹肉饼，
举起你的手。
I can't hear your meeping
with these headphones on.
我听不到你的喵喵声
戴着这些耳机。
Thank Neptune.
Aah!
感谢海王星。
啊啊！
No!
不！
No! Not my headphones!
不！不是我的耳机！
The meeps.
I can hear the horrible meeps.
米普们。
我能听到可怕的米普声。
All: Meep, meep, hungry.
全体：喵，喵，饿了。
- More meeps?
- 更多米普？
All: Meep.
全体：米普。
- [gasps] Anchovy rumble!
- [喘气]凤尾鱼隆隆声！
[upbeat tense music]
[欢快紧张的音乐]
♪ ♪
all: Meep.
All: Meep.
全体：米普。
♪ ♪
all: Meep. Argh!
全体：米普。啊！
[all angrily meep]
[全都愤怒地喵]
- Meep.
- 米普。
- Meeeeep.
- 嗯嗯。
- My bad. I meant meep, meep.
- 我的错。我的意思是米普，米普。
- Oh, meep.
- 哦，米普。
[sniffs]
[嗅嗅]
- Meep, meep!
I thought that was you.
- 米普，米普！
我以为那就是你。
- The whole world
has gone insane!
- 整个世界
已经疯了！
[all meep happily]
[大家都开心]
I can't take it anymore.
我再也受不了了。
That is the last meep!
那是最后的meep！
[distressed panting]
[心疼的喘气]
[phone ringing]
[电话铃声]
[bright Italian melody]
【明亮的意大利旋律】
- Serba's World of Pizza.
What do you want?
- 塞尔维亚的披萨世界。
你想要什么？
- I'd like an extra, extra,
extra large pizza
- 我想要一个额外的，额外的，
超大披萨
sent to the Krusty Krab
as soon as possible.
发送至蟹堡王
尽快。
- Hey, you want-a a pizza
as soon-a as possible,
- 嘿，你想要一个披萨
尽快，
you got it, Calimaro.
你明白了，卡利马罗。
- Aah! Ha.
- 啊啊！哈。
Nobody's turning me
into a faux-chovy.
没人让我转
变成假chovy。
[laughs]
[笑]
[meeping]
- Pizza delivery.
[嘀咕]
- 披萨外送。
All: Huh?
全体：啊？
Both: Pizza?
[all meeping]
两人：披萨？
[大家都在嘀咕]
[all inhale deeply]
all: Mmm.
[所有人深吸一口气]
全体：嗯。
- Mmm, that smells good.
- 嗯，闻起来很香。
[both laugh]
[两人都笑了]
both: Huh?
两人：啊？
All: Oh!
- Phew.
全体：哦！
- 唷。
I thought we'd never snap out
of that faux-chovy thing.
我以为我们永远不会分手
那个假chovy的东西。
- Sorry, Mr. Krabs.
- 对不起，蟹老板。
I didn't realize how easy it is
to get swept up
我没有意识到这有多容易
被卷走
into a meep mentality.
进入一种meep心态。
- It's not your fault, boy-o.
- 这不是你的错，小伙子。
We're just lucky that pizza is
the anchovies' natural enemy.
我们很幸运，披萨是
凤尾鱼的天敌。
- Yeah, whoever ordered
that pie saved our lives.
- 是的，无论是谁订购的
那块馅饼救了我们的命。
- And we shouldn't let it go
to waste.
- 我们不应该放手
浪费。
It's still hot.
- Oh-ho-ho!
天气还很热。
- 哦嗬嗬！
[grunts] Gah!
[咕噜声] 啊！
What? No anchovies?
什么？没有凤尾鱼吗？
- All that meeping
made me hungry too.
- 所有那些喵喵叫声
也让我饿了。
Mr. Squidward, we need
some paper plates out here.
章鱼哥先生，我们需要
这里有一些纸盘。
- Squidward? Uh, are you here?
- 章鱼哥？呃，你在吗？
- Now just where is
that lazy bum
- 现在就在哪里
那个懒惰的流浪汉
while all this is going on?
当这一切发生的时候？
[all meeping]
[大家都在嘀咕]
- Meep.
- 米普。
[light music]
[轻音乐]
♪ ♪